Dennis (Chengchen) Wu

3535 Lebon Drive, San Diego, CA, 92122

c8wu@ucsd.edu / personal@denncc.com | (858) 344-3720 | linkedin.com/in/denncc

SUMMARY

I'm a third year Data Science student who not only has endless interest in machine learning, but also backend development and business communication. Three years of discipline in the bachelor program in data science has trained me to a team-oriented grinder and prepared me with various situations in data science.

EDUCATION

University of California, San Diego

• Overall GPA: 3.7,

9/2018 - Expected June 2022 B.S. Data Science

EXPERIENCE

Nakamura Partners, San Diego, United States

3/2020 -

Present

Founding Member/Full-time Backend Developer

- Leading engineer in the company; responsible for the cloud computing and database
- Product manager and major backend developer for the company's patented Graph Database Based Emergency Response System
- Serve as the company's representative that negotiates international outreach; once almost closing a deal of mask importation between a mask producer based in China and a local hospital in San Diego during the local shortage of masks.

Volunteer Administrator of Online Career Server

10/2020 - Present

- Contribute to Chinese immigrant community by managing a 2300-person Discord server.
- Primary objective is to help the new graduate from college be successful in the first years of their career at Fortune 500 technology companies.
- Optimize the interactive pipeline that allows for custom Discord bot services and anonymous messaging; ensure the daily active message with the number of at least 1,000.

Xiantao Customer Insight Research and Big Data Co.,Ltd, Chongqing, China *Intern, Algorithm Engineer*

7/2019-9/2019

• Endeavor in Model Fitting of the company's first IoT product - Xrush, a kid-targeted toothbrush striving to keep track of users' daily brushing habits. Reduce the prediction error of the model that predicts tooth brush movement by 10%

SKILLS & ACTIVITIES

Python, Scikit-learn, Postgresql, Redis, Java, Neo4j, Cassandra, MongoDB, Chinese (Native Level)